Frederik Pohl Papers
Frederik Pohl Papers
- Fanzines, conference material, other fan publications
  - Science fiction title changes, 1965 (Box 21)
  - Science fiction weekly, 1967-1968; nos. 182-192, 198, 200, 202-203, 205-206, 208-209, 216-221, 223-226, 229 (Box 21)
  - Science Fiction Writers of America (SFWA), miscellaneous (Box 21)
  - Science fiction yearbook, 1964 (Box 21)
  - The secondary universe, 1968; national conference (Box 21)
  - Second mercenary, 1965; also known as Ben-Crud-Yo #16 (Box 21)
  - The seldom seen, 1967; no. 2 (Box 21)
  - Shangri-l'affaires, 1968; nos. 72, 75 (Box 21)
  - Sirruish, 1967; undated; no. 4 and unnumbered/undated issue (Box 21)
  - Son of tightbeam, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Speculation, 1966-1969; nos. 14-15, 20-21 (Box 21)
  - Speculative bulletin, no. 4 (Box 21)
  - Star Trek Fan Club, 1967; miscellaneous (Box 21)
  - Starwitch Louhi rides again, 1967 (Box 21)
  - Stroon, 1966-1967; nos. 1-7 (Box 21)
  - The swinging bore, 1958; no. 4 (Box 21)
  - The Syracon sentinel, 1965-1966 (Box 21)
  - Syracuse, 1965; 3 issues (Box 21)
  - Syzygy, 1968; no. 1 (Box 21)
  - Thru the haze, 1968; 2 issues (Box 21)
  - Tightbeam, 1966-1969; nos. 40-45, 47-48, 54, 56 (Box 21)
  - Tintinnabulations, 1968; no. 2 (Box 21)
  - Tokon, 1963; 1965,; 1967; annual meetings and miscellaneous items (Box 21)
  - Tolkien journal, 1965; no. 2 (Box 21)
  - Tricon (24th WorldCon), miscellaneous (Box 21)
    See also World Science Fiction Convention, 24th, Cleveland OH, below.
  - Trumpet, 1965-1968; nos. 1-3, 5-7 (Box 22)
  - Trypod, 1968; no. 2 (Box 22)
  - Tumbrils, 1949; no. 21 (Box 22)
  - Twilight zine, 1966-1967; nos. 16-22 (Box 22)
  - Uchujin, 1967-1968; nos. 115-119 (Box 22)
  - Vantage point, 1945; no. 2 (Box 22)
  - Westercon, 1965; 1966; annual west coast science fantasy conference (Box 22)
  - Witzend, 1966-1968; nos. 1-5 (Box 22)
  - Wizard, 1966; no. 2 (Box 22)
  - Wizard and warrior, 1965; vol. 1, no. 1; also known as Galactic Outpost #9 (Box 22)
  - World Science Fiction Conventions
    - 20th WorldCon (Chicon III), 1962; See Convention Annual, Chicon III edition and The proceedings: ChiCon III, above.
    - 21st WorldCon (Discon), 1963; See Convention Annual, Discon Edition, above.
    - 22nd WorldCon (Pacificon 2), 1964; See Pacificon 2 (22nd WorldCon), above.
    - 24th WorldCon (TriCon), 1966 (Box 22)
      See also Tricon (24th WorldCon), above.
    - 25th WorldCon (NyCon), 1967; See NyCon (25th WorldCon), above.
    - 26th WorldCon (Baycon), 1968; See Baycon (26th WorldCon), above.
    - 27th WorldCon (St. Louiscon), 1969; See Saint Louiscon (27th WorldCon), above.
  - Writer's exchange, 1965; nos. 1-2 (Box 22)
  - WRR, 1968; vol. 4, no. 2 (Box 22)
  - The WSFA journal, 1966-1968; nos. 21-22, 36, 54 (Box 23)
  - Xenon, 1968; no. 1 (Box 23)
  - Zenith speculation, 1965-1966; nos. 9-13 (Box 23)
  - Zobee, 1967; vol. 1, no. 1 (Box 23)
  - Le Zombie, 1968; no. 66 (Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 23)